yeah come on tell you more magnetic
yeah um good day um we're talking with
Joe about a an
electromagnetic generator motor motor
and
Generator
[Music]
oh never been bloody wrong he's not
talking about it's talking about your
one and just giving you a few ideas
about magnetic fs and how
they okay so in experience with playing
with different Motors like this and
different other things you see here the
field effects is laying down at at um uh
sideways okay and if you want to get
down there a magnet a compass magnetic
fields and everything else do not run
up and
down your electricity is north
south okay that's all they know about AR
about East and West they don't cover
that electrical field they don't talk
about up and down they don't talk about
any other degrees in between so la and
DC and everything else only come from
North and South Pole which
is horizontal is that right yeah that's
vertical okay up and down vertical so
when you are rotating a through a
magnetic field and everything else
you're lining up your magnets and
something like that and what we found is
um what I found in in differences is by
trying to do same things like this they
work a h a lot better while standing
them ight so that they stand up vertical
and your magnetic fields are actually
rotating around horizontally and they
they match in and and and spin free and
line up better and you're not fighting
against gravity and up and down and all
these other fields so he's just getting
it on here for the table
okay so you standed up we found out you
can break these down to a hell of a lot
smaller and output a hell of a lot more
because the actual feels in the Earth
are assisting you instead of going
against do that make sense to you
yourself as much as I can absorb it yeah
so within other people's ones and
everything Els what they've taken is Big
generators like this similar okay they
met different ways they talk you know
talk about same things and so on like
that instead of putting massive amounts
of electricity in only putting very
minut amount of to
excite yeah small what's your small man
11 start but then decreases all the way
down to that's a small amount this
Fell's putting these other fellas what
we've played with and everything else
and what we were doing is um we were
only down to at the most
12v no more than 12vt input but it's
outputting a hell of a lot more and the
generator uh you know it excites you
know your magnetic fields and it excites
and everything else and it's putting out
um massive amounts of electricity like
frame way over way over
240 way over right so you've got to
bring it back so you're only exciting
with a a DC field input and you get
massive AC you know filled out all right
so the um now breaking if you shoot into
here this thing here was about the same
size as some other people what we know
uh in you know sizing of a generator
laying down sideways generating okay and
um then what they've got now is just the
idea of changing it turning it upright
instead of laying down they're turning
it upright and their machine is only a
little bit bigger than that now compared
to that to that and it's outputting 10
times the amount of what the big fun
could ever put in
okay now I don't want to on your tape
and everything else mention who what
when we're why cuz it's somebody else's
stuff okay so within this you're
actually fighting against gravities and
your feeli your magnetic fields do not
run this way you what I'm understand
they don't so you want to take away all
that load and everything else you you
stand it up and you rotate it that way
and you change the way that your magnet
your coils are
and your coils and your magnets and and
um and so on like that will tap into so
that the Earth will actually assist does
that make sense at all yeah that makes
yeah you got to fit in with the you fit
in so you're not fighting against yeah
fitting with Earth Harmony now
while that um I'll take you up and I'll
show you some other things what occurs
through magnetic fields which you can
use for different things and and these
magnetic fields and everything else are
only working properly and everything
Gose because of the moisture water or
h2o what you call it in our atmosphere
here okay so that's what I said to use
it's on tape if you have a compass and a
compass is magnets and your compass say
a needle South Pole will point to the
north okay and so on and but what will
affect that you say that your your
compass needle it's a magnet and the
Earth's magnetic field is strong so
you're just going to keep walking with
your compass till you hit the North
Pole no you cross any water and that
water is rotating if you want to check
it your your water underneath the ground
and and everywhere else even on top of
the ground is rotating over you know
rolling and it rolls three ways you've
only got two systems here what you got
is only a North and the South Pole
that's all pushing a
pool your water your fields in the earth
don't just have two
poles okay they tap into a hell of a lot
more poles what they don't use you don't
consider so if this was a compass and
you actually crossed the cross water and
if that water and someone like that was
um uh one kind of say you got clean and
dirty water as such your Compass if it's
clean water it your clean water will
carry a negative charge now if it's
running from west to east and everything
else what'll happen is you got a South
Pole tip on your compass that will
attract to the
north
okay okay if you've got dirty water and
so on you got a South Pole here and
dirty water is south pole and your South
Pole water is going the same way and
everything else what will actually
happen is it will not attract to the
direction of your your dirty water you
know it will push away so if you yeah it
does you cross over dirty water and your
compass South Pole tip is going to aim
and run long ways wherever you cross
that water okay and the other thing what
can happen too is crossing the water a
certain way with your compass the same
as Crossing it it use the compass and
crossed a
magnet it repolarizes
it if your compass now can turn around
the opposite damn way because you
repolarized your magnets you understand
so now if you're looking at what you
really got in your magnets and
everything else is your your North Pole
should be rejecting itself from the
North Pole but now your North Pole of
your compass is actually attracting to
the North Pole and your South Pole is
actually attracting to the
cell
okay now you well they might tell you
that all you've done is youve changed
your North Pole magnet to South no you
haven't what you actually got is to the
North Pole tip on your on your compass
has it's not one piece magnet see if you
got one piece magnet you'd have North
you'd have South on this end North on
that end but these are only tip pieces
so to do that you would have a South
Pole small piece and just Bri just at
the magnetic piece you would have North
Pole at the other
side and now you've got the same on the
other end of your
compass okay now when it repolarizes
what actually happens is the she flips
in without
changing she flips that field and what
actually happens is you have North Pole
right you've got North Pole facing
to stuff up
you got nor facing